## About me

I'm a ZCPE (Zend Certified PHP Engineer) familiar with agile model of software development cycle. I've been working with PHP since 2009, I'm passionate for open-source, patterns, tests and source code well written. Always looking for best practices, new technologies and methodologies to improve my workflow and bring great results to the project and to my customer.

## Experience

## GetYourGuide Senior Software Engineer

Currently

- Impacting and changing the way how millions of travellers connect to the places they visit, in combination with rigorous A/B testing to craft an unbeatable e-commerce, in numbers during the last months as one team we created about 20 experiments and I worked with 4 of them, in which the last one increased the conversion rate in almost 2%;
- Aligning product with technical decisions, having the customer at first and proposing changes while thinking about myself and my parents as travellers have guided me to influence in a killer feature to contact us through whatsapp in which our customers can get support from their smartphone, it increased the second customer purchase considerably and helped us to retain customers;
- Doing interviews, providing long detailed feeback about talents and suggesting improvements to the process in order to hire the best engineers and so develop a really good product;
- Test driven oriented, impacting the way that the company sees test and so bringing the quality of the product to the next level.

FlixBus Senior PHP Developer 2017 - 2018

- Changing the life of approximately one billion of people commuting, spending their weekends, building remote relationships, visiting relatives, and discovering the world;
- We improved the response time for retrieving a cart in almost 70% by extracting the code from the monolith to a new micro-service-oriented architecture;
- Volunteer to be a facilitator in agile ceremonies such as retrospective and spring review;
- Responsible for taking decisions from a technical perspective regarding our domain.

NeoGrid Senior PHP Developer 2015 - 2017

- Created a web application using Material Design and AngularJS to the front-end and Silex to the back-end, which automated the sales of the WebEDI solution;
- Implemented improvements, bug fixes and integrations with NeoGrid solutions using REST APIs;
- Added the Vagrant tool to use with my team in order to use environments identical with the production environment;
- Evangelist of best practices of programming following the existent PSRs and implementing unit test in the projects;
- Reference in my team to projects that was written in PHP and AngularJS.

Humantech PHP Developer 2015-2015

- Led the team (five workers) as assistant manager of the programming department when the manager was not present;
- Added unit tests in critical project parts, reducing considerable the amount of bugs and increasing the quality of projects;
- Created an e-learning platform using the gamification concepts.

A2C PHP Developer 2013 - 2014

- Created a CMS to the 3M brand using the gamification concepts and fully focused on SEO, that resulted in three times more access to the
  website in few months;
- Created a software to monitor the reputation of political candidates in social networks, that give more visibility on medias to the agency;
- Reference in my team to projects that was written in Symfony 2;
- Responsible to manage the Amazon Web Services EC2, RDS and S3.

## Education

UNISOCIESC BSc Information Systems 2011 - 2014

- Honor as the best student of the course;
- The final paper is based on a tool created to be used by professionals that are studying to achieve the ZCPE certification, the project is open-source and is available on GitHub, the project is hosted by "DigitalOcean" as a sponsor.